Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XL is arranged in 34 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XL. GRAND LODGE OFFICE EMPLOYEES
  - Sub-Series 280-0. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - General, 1961-1963 (Box 463, Folder 26)
    - General, 1935-1944 (Box 463, Folder 27)
    - General, 1922-1932 (Box 464, Folder 1)
    - Death of Hartman Barber, 1959 (Box 464, Folder 2)
    - General, 1956-1960 (Box 464, Folder 3)
      July 1956-60.
    - General, 1953-1956 (Box 464, Folder 4)
      July 1953-June 1956.
    - General, 1951-1953 (Box 464, Folder 5)
      April 1951-June 1953.
    - General, 1948-1951 (Box 464, Folder 6)
      1948-March 1951.
    - General, 1945-1947 (Box 464, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 280-1. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Vacations, 1958-1963 (Box 464, Folder 8)
    - Vacations, 1933-1957 (Box 464, Folder 9)
    - Vacations, 1921-1932 (Box 464, Folder 10)
    - Vacations, 1930-1932 (Box 464, Folder 11)
    - Vacations, 1962 (Box 464, Folder 12)
    - Vacations, 1961 (Box 464, Folder 13-14)
    - Vacations, 1960 (Box 464, Folder 15-16)
    - Vacations, 1959 (Box 464, Folder 17-18)
    - Vacations, 1958 (Box 464, Folder 19-20)
    - Vacations, 1957 (Box 464, Folder 21-22)
    - Vacations, 1956 (Box 464, Folder 23-24)
    - Vacations, 1943 (Box 464, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 280-2. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Leaves of Absence and Sick Leave, 1935-1957 (Box 464, Folder 26)
    - Leaves of Absence and Sick Leave, 1944 (Box 464, Folder 27)
    - Leaves of Absence and Sick Leave, 1925-1929 (Box 464, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 280-3. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Service Letter, 1921 (Box 464, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 280-4. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Assignment of Duties, 1925-1964 (Box 464, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 280-5. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Instructions, 1959-1962 (Box 464, Folder 31)
      December 1959-62.
    - Instructions, 1940-1945 (Box 464, Folder 32)
    - Instructions, 1924-1932 (Box 464, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 280-6. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Leave of Absence for Voting, 1921-1922 (Box 464, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 280-7. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Special Holidays, 1921-1925 (Box 464, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 280-8. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Payroll, 1964-1965 (Box 464, Folder 36)
      1964-August 1965.
    - Payroll, 1962-1963 (Box 465, Folder 1)
      October 1962-63.
    - Payroll, 1958-1962 (Box 465, Folder 2)
      1958-September 1962.
    - Payroll, 1932-1957 (Box 465, Folder 3)
    - Payroll, 1963 (Box 465, Folder 4)
    - Payroll, 1962 (Box 465, Folder 5)
    - Payroll, 1961 (Box 465, Folder 6)
    - Payroll, 1960 (Box 465, Folder 7)
    - Payroll, 1959 (Box 465, Folder 8)
    - Payroll, 1957-1958 (Box 465, Folder 9)
    - Payroll, 1953-1956 (Box 465, Folder 10)
    - Payroll, 1952 (Box 465, Folder 11)
    - Payroll, 1950-1951 (Box 465, Folder 12)
    - Payroll, 1949 (Box 465, Folder 13)
    - Payroll, 1943-1948 (Box 465, Folder 14)
    - Payroll, 1935-1942 (Box 465, Folder 15)
    - Payroll, 1922-1927 (Box 465, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 280-9. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Seniority, 1922-1926 (Box 465, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 280-10. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Brotherhood Membership -1957 (Box 465, Folder 18)
    - Brotherhood Membership -1922 (Box 465, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 280-11. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Temporary Employees, 1922-1934 (Box 465, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 280-12. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Working Conditions, 1921-1925 (Box 465, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 280-13. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Rates of Pay, 1954-1957 (Box 465, Folder 22)
    - Rates of Pay, 1950-1953 (Box 465, Folder 23)
    - Rates of Pay, 1928-1929 (Box 465, Folder 24)
    - Rates of Pay, 1944-1949 (Box 465, Folder 25)
      June 1944-49.
    - Rates of Pay, 1932 (Box 465, Folder 26)
    - Rates of Pay, 1924-1941 (Box 466, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 280-16. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Research Department, 1934-1937 (Box 466, Folder 2)
    - Research Department, 1925-1928 (Box 466, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 280-17. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Resignations, 1925-1950 (Box 466, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 280-18. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Assistant to the Grand President, 1925-1935 (Box 466, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 280-19. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Extra Employees, 1934 (Box 466, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 280-20. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Injuries, 1925-1926 (Box 466, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 280-21. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Vacancies, 1925-1926 (Box 466, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 280-22. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Bids on Positions, 1949-1959 (Box 466, Folder 9)
    - Bids on Positions, 1926-1934 (Box 466, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 280-23. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - General, 1926-1933 (Box 466, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 280-25. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Bulletins, 1953-1957 (Box 466, Folder 12)
      March 11, 1953-December 28, 1957.
    - Bulletins, 1963-1964 (Box 466, Folder 13)
    - Bulletins, 1960-1962 (Box 466, Folder 14)
    - Bulletins, 1957-1959 (Box 466, Folder 15)
      November 1957-59.
    - Bulletins, 1957-1958 (Box 466, Folder 16)
    - Bulletins, 1955-1957 (Box 466, Folder 17)
      1955-October 28, 1957.
    - Bulletins, 1952-1954 (Box 466, Folder 18)
      March 1952-54.
    - Bulletins, 1940-1946 (Box 466, Folder 19)
    - Bulletins, 1947-1952 (Box 466, Folder 20)
      1947-February 1952.
    - Bulletins, 1928-1939 (Box 466, Folder 21)
    - Bulletins, 1946-1952 (Box 466, Folder 22)
    - Bulletins, 1926-1927 (Box 466, Folder 23)
    - Bulletins, 1925 (Box 466, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 280-26. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Addresses of Employees Laid-Off, 1926-1934 (Box 466, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 280-27. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - General Chairmen, 1927-1939 (Box 466, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 280-28. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Position of Stenographer, Vice Grand President's Office for Express Division, 1928-1929 (Box 466, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 280-29. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Christmas Presents, 1929 (Box 466, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 280-30. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Notice to Return to Service, 1929 (Box 466, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 280-31. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - System Board Per Capita Tax, 1930-1935 (Box 466, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 280-32. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Displacements, 1931 (Box 466, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 280-34. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Special Assistant to the Grand President, 1933-1944 (Box 466, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 280-35. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Special Assistant to the Grand President for Legislative Matters, 1933 (Box 466, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 280-36. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Stenographers' Symbols, 1933 (Box 466, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 280-37. Grand Lodge Office Employees
    - Supplemental Retirement Plan, 1945-1955 (Box 466, Folder 35)